Yakantha Idol
The third one is a friend.
The third is a friend?
Yes, sir.
That sounds like a lot of friends.
I have a lot of friends.
Really? At school?
School, of course.
Do you enjoy school?
School is fun. Except for studying.
I like recess and lunch time the best.
Bento?
Yes, a lunch box.
Junior high school
So even friends are very important to you.
Yes, they are. I don't know, since I joined Ebichu.
I can't go to school as often as I used to.
But then I realized how important friends are.
Why is that?
I don't know, we talk about stupid things.
Or laughing at something super weird.
Friends with whom you can do silly things like that...
I think it's something that you can only do with the kids you've been with since elementary school.
I really want to meet them again.
NakanishiHow many people are in your group?
Is it one side?
I didn't know they were called "front page. I've learned a little bit about it.
One side.
So you're on the front page?
Are you a regular member?
Yes, we are. I guess there are four of us on the front page.
Four.
Since elementary school?
Yes, that's right. That's since elementary school, since junior high school.
Eh. Huh? What is it among friends? Right now.
Is there anything that's popular?
The word that's popular is "male.
Males are in vogue?
I just said it out of the blue.
Like, "Do something about it.
Do something about it.
It goes with the conversation.
Usually, people would say something like, "Okay," or "I understand.
I suddenly said "male.
And everyone fell in love with it.
So now everyone at school is using the word "male.
That's great.
It made me happy.
You're the trend leader.
You made Haeli?
Yes, I did.
I was happy.
I heard that everyone calls them males.
Next time, say "male" like I said before.
No, that's not good.
I want you to keep the camera rolling.
Suddenly say "male.
I said "male" all of a sudden.
What's wrong? I'm sure they'd be like, "What's going on?
Mr. Fujii is fine.
Are you all right, Mr. Fujii?
Mr. Fujii, I'm fine.
Mr. Fujii, you're all right, aren't you?
Suddenly he's a male.
You seem to be saying something serious, don't you?
Do you have a tendency to talk a lot?
You do talk about something, don't you?
Somehow.
I think it's interesting.
Oh, I'm kind of funny. I'd like to have a camera on me.
You call him a male?
I'd like to see Fujii's reaction when I suddenly call him a male.
But could you relate?
Do you have a little bit of Kasahara in you, Headmaster?
I understand a little.
Male.
Oshi!
Hush!
Isn't Shizuoka farther?
Wait a minute.
I see. I'll stop.
I'm sorry.
This program...
Mr. Ren.
Mr. Burton Custom
Mr. Tomoki
No Nickname
This program was provided by Nozoe Mayu Naoshi
Thank you very much.